{
    "id": "a9dd406f6a3a49e98c26107fda15516b",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The villagers are steeped ............................... ignorance and superstition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e1811134a41742e49cea5d47a0edc31e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Their customs are similar to ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "our",
                "ours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cd75c57c62324ffb8d307de5344ef35e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Solomon succeeded .................................. the throne of David.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0f753e2dbe44e2a8157f5e70ea92ed9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am suspicious ................................ his true intentions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fcd36f7b2679484f9c114f21b76e0cbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He tampered ................................ the office files.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d6e9d54c54d94a30b674e9e30f706a3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can testify ............................. his honesty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e44c0059a4144a9b53c2fefff47de6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired ............................... reminding him about this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf60f58751354eccab152c8501a24638"
        },
        {
            "question": "He touched ................................ unemployment and allied problems in his speech.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "upon",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef702653cd2042a7ac9cd45a6bf96752"
        },
        {
            "question": "Be always true .................................... your conscience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5ca5068b351749698fe575dd9fac1016"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is wanting ................................... sympathy and understanding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5473e9b531b9437d88e49b37351b4557"
        }
    ]
}